<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ISTE RIT CHAPTER</title>
    <description>The Indian Society for Technical Education is a national, professional, non-profit Society registered under the Indian Societies Registration Act</description>
    <link>https://abhi1401.github.io/isterit/</link>
    <atom:link href="https://abhi1401.github.io/isterit/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>ISTE State Convention</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The always leading richness of ISTE has brought about several pinnacles over the years. And as a further lead to its flourishing,  its 16th ISTE State Convention for the year 2018 as SANGRAH ‘18 was held at GCE Kannur. RIT chapter did its best for this convention and was in the top 15 list from around 40+ colleges. We are proud to  announce that our students Shinoy Jayan K.D. &amp;amp; Sanjay Krishna J have secured 1st place in technical event named ‘you wire’. It was a wiring competition where circuit lay out and condition to be obtained are given to the participant and the evaluation was strictly based on output, time taken for work, quality of work etc. 
This highlights the interest of students to participate in more events and also a sign of perfect utilisation of ISTE’s opportunities. We are glad that we could be a platform for them and we congratulate the winners and also those who took part in Sangrah18  from ISTE RIT chapter. We wish we could achieve more.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2018 05:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>https://abhi1401.github.io/isterit/State-Convention</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://abhi1401.github.io/isterit/State-Convention</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Techvridhi</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;rit-students-bagged-prizes-from-iit-kharagpur&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;RIT Students bagged prizes from IIT Kharagpur&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Events&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Inter-Collegiate Quiz Competition&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Inter-Collegiate Debate Competition&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The students of semester 4, AKHIL SURESH, AKHIL MURALI, AJIN KP, JINO THOMAS, TESWIN JOSE of Civil department participated in the National Championship for Mechanical and Civil representing the ISTE RIT chapter as a part of Global Entrepreneurship Summit conducted at IIT Kharagpur held in 2nd and 3rd Feb 2018.  They were awarded 2nd position for the same.
_ Hearty congratulations for the shinning stars._&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2018 05:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>https://abhi1401.github.io/isterit/Techvridhi</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://abhi1401.github.io/isterit/Techvridhi</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
